Today's bonus question is, how do you define yourself politically?
That is today's bonus question.
How do you define yourself politically?
Now, this question is coming from, I'm seeing people say that they don't understand why I'm
calling myself a radical, that basically I can only be a conservative or a liberal.
I can't be anything else.
And that is 100% false.
I will also later in the show for our critical thinking exercise, I will explain what a black
radical is and what the black radical tradition is.
I would love for you all to drop in the comments, how do you define yourself politically?
You see, we don't push the algorithm here by allowing negativity, by allowing trolls,
by allowing nonsense.
We push the algorithm here by engaging intellectually.
How do you define yourself politically?
And if you want to add a little extra razzle dazzle, you can put what got you there.
You know, maybe you were something and then you became something else, et cetera, et cetera,
et cetera.
So, you know, as D Steel TV says, you can be radical, you can be a revolutionary, you can
be a progressive, you can be a centrist, you can be conservative.
There's levels of the political spectrum, all right?
So many levels.
Then you have Kiki who says, I'm Democratic on paper, but only because a third party has
never succeeded.
Definitely not Republican, but the Democrats aren't for us either.
Well, Kiki, baby, you know we about that life here at Amanda Land, okay?
Anyone here who has an Amanda Land passport knows that we are not a bipartisan community
at all.
We are not a bipartisan community at all.
So make sure that you drop in and leave your answer to the bonus question in the comments.
Amen.